Stanislav Raskumandrin

+7 812 987–38–43, S raskumandrin,

raskumas,

stas@raskumandrin.ru.

Objective

I work with Perl for 14 years and with SQL for almost 16 years, and I really like them. I create and support information systems not only using coding but also taking advantage of communicating with team and consumers. Also I watch over new trends which are concern my field of knowledge.

Experience

Public Git repository: https://bitbucket.org/raskumandrin

https://raskumandrin.github.io/ Blog:

Limited company "Epam". 2016—2020. External project: Health LRP application development and maintenance (Perl, Bash; Oracle; Solaris, Red Hat; AWS; Vim, tmux; SVN, Git; Chef, Jenkins). https://epam.com/

Saint Petersburg State Company "Mineral". 2014—2016. Development of tracking and analytical system for air pollution inspection, development of device drivers (Perl; Tiny Core Linux). http://noreurgeoch.net/index.php?goto=/ACTIVITY RUS/MONITORING RUS/AIR RUS

Limited company "Torgovy Dom Severo-Zapadny". 2015. Development of online-shop platform (Perl; MySOL; CentOS; Atlassian stack; JIRA, Confluence, Bitbucket, HipChat), http://www.220-volt.ru/

Limited company "EuroLife" . 2013. Development of order automation system for construction company (Perl, Mojolicious; MySQL; JavaScript; Bootstrap 3). https://stas.raskumandrin.ru/complicated-calculator/

Limited company "Inter". 2006—2016. Design, development and maintenance of online-shop platform. (Perl, Mojolicious; MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite; Debian, Apache, Nginx; Memcached; Sphinx; AWS). Implementation of sms-mail service, automation accounting of suppliers' warehouses, etc.

Limited company "Solus". 2012: Websites development with company's perl-based CMS. http://solus.ru/web-cms.html

Limited company "DeltaIncom". 2010—2011. Development of government registries extracts system (Perl, MySql). http://deltaincom.ru.

Limited company. 2008—2011. Development of online banking system. (Perl, MySql). Intranet.

Closed joint-stock company "Medi". 2005—2011. Maintenance of corporate information system (MS SQL 6.5, 2000); BI reporting (Transact-SQL); programming user interface (Delphi 6).

Limited company "Rad", closed joint-stock company "Expoline" and non-profit charitable organization "Hesed". 2002—2004. Developer (Delphi 6, Delphi 7, InterBase, MS Access, administration of a computer network).

Education

1999—2005: Saint Petersburg Electrotechnical University "LETI" (ETU). The Faculty of Computing Technologies and Informatics. Diploma Engineer Degree Programmes Applied mathematics.

1989—1999: Saint Petersburg School. 10 and 11 grades were mathematical.

1996—1998: Course of English language.

2011: Accounting courses.

2019: AWS Technical Professional, https://aws.amazon.com/ru/partners/training/path-tech-pro/.

2019: English Assessment. Speaking: B2, writing: B2 (Upper-Intermediate).

References

Available upon request.